cabionline.com 2019-12-22

# Privacy Policy | Cabi Clothing

## Privacy Policy _Last Updated: June 1, 2009_

### 1\. **INTRODUCTION**

#### 1.1. **Purpose of Policy**

Welcome to the cabi, LLC family of web sites. cabi, LLC (”us,” “we,” or “cabi”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of its website (the “Website”). We created this Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Website, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Policy is only applicable to the Website, and not to any other web sites that you may be able to access from the Website, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy.

#### 1.2. **Notice Concerning Children**

We are a general audience site, and do not direct any of our content specifically at children 13 years of age or under. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a Website user is age 13 or under, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user’s account.

#### 2\. **INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES**

#### 2.1. **What Basic Information Do We Collect?**

In operating the Website, we may include registration, online surveys, and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, addresses, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, date of birth, and other contact information, bank information of consultants, credit card information for purchases, as well as other user profile information, including without limitation, gender, education, occupation and images and videos you submit.

#### 2.2. **What Additional Information Do We Collect?**

(a) Automatic Collection. Our servers automatically recognize visitors’ domain names and IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet). No personal information about you is revealed in this process. The Website may also gather anonymous “traffic data” that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer.

(b) Cookies. From time to time, we may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to our Website. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor do we employ any data capture mechanisms on our Website other than cookies. Cookies help us learn which areas of our site are useful and which areas need improvement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Website may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

#### 2.3. How we collect your Information?

If you are a cabi customer or a Hostess, your personal data may be provided to us by the cabi Stylist who took your order or who organized or attended a cabi event that you hosted or attended.

We may collect personal data provided to us by your cabi Stylist or Hostess. This information may have been gathered by importing the Stylists or Hostesses personal email contacts list. This information will be stored in a safe and secure manner and only used for the sole purpose of contacting you about cabi shows, promotions, and reminders.

**Personal email Contact Import Specific Privacy Statement:**  
This privacy statement describes how cabi collects and uses the information you provide in your personal email contacts account via the cabi “Online Hostess Planner” application. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your information and how you can access and update this information.

Collection and Use

We collect the following personal information from your personal email contacts account:

  * Contacts’ names
  * Contacts’ email
  * Contacts’ telephones
  * Contacts’ organization
  * Contacts’ postal address
  * Contacts’ birthday
  * Contacts’ gender

We use this information to:

  1. Populate your personal email contact data into your Stylist’s cabi customer management tool
  2. Create show invites from your Stylist’s show calendar for the imported contacts
  3. Send show confirmation emails, show cancellation emails, show update emails or show reminder emails to the contacts imported from personal email contacts – prior to sending out such emails your consent will be sought each time.

We will only use this information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us. We do not add or modify any personal email contact information using your cabi account.

#### 3\. **USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION**

#### 3.1. **What Do We Do With Collected Information?**

(a) Personal Information. We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. We may use your personal information to verify your identity or to follow up with transactions initiated on the Website. We may also use your contact information to inform you of any changes to the Website, to send you additional information about cabi, or to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you are a consultant and give your permission during the account registration process, we may share your contact information on the Website _._ We don’t give information to any partners or for any promotions. If you choose to post information on the Website in a public forum, your name, location and comment (all as entered by you) will be displayed to all users of the Website to facilitate interaction among users. General users’ email addresses are never revealed to other users; provided, however, Consultants’ have the option of revealing their email address and phone number on the Website.

(b) Anonymous Information. We use anonymous information to analyze our Website traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

(c) Use of Cookies. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, or for other purposes.

(d) Disclosure of Personal Information. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on cabi or its affiliates, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of cabi or the users of the Website, or (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Website.

(e) Sale of Assets. In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of our company or other companies or assets, including the information collected through the Website. If cabi or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer.

(f) Access to Information / Opting-Out. If you have opted to receive email from us, you may unsubscribe at any time by using the opt-out option at the bottom of the email.

#### 4\. **SECURITY**

The Website has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

#### 5\. **SITE AREAS BEYOND OUR CONTROL**

#### 5.1. **Public Forums**

The Website includes interactive forums for the exchange of information, ideas and opinions. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information.

#### 5.2. **Third Party Websites**

The Web Site may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

#### 6\. **CONTACT INFORMATION AND POLICY UPDATES**

#### 6.1. **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to the Website, or if you would like to have us remove your information from our database, please feel contact us at the following email address: [privacy@cabiexperience.com](mailto:privacy@cabiexperience.com).

#### 6.2. **Updates and Changes**

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Website and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.
